♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hallmark
Original Pictures presents
an instant family classic:
Summers With My Slow Brother,
starring a cast of people
who make you say "Oh,"
because you didn't think
they were still acting.
For example, Grant Show.
Oh.
Rachael Leigh Cook.
David Faustino.
Oh.
And Robin Tunney.
Huh?
The bald-headed chick
from Empire Records.
Oh.
Guys, could you
turn that down?
I'm trying to study
for the SAT.
Hey, careful, Meg.
Remember what happened
the last time I had to choose
between you and the TV.
Don't worry.
Meg's holding our stuff.
Meg, don't drink
that soda!
I'm serious, you guys.
I haven't been doing well
on these practice tests,
and I need to improve my score
to get into a good college.
You're in high school,
sweetie.
You should be much more
concerned about your weight
than your SAT scores.
Don't listen to her, Meg.
Academics are
extremely important.
Are the SATs essential?
Vital? Crucial?
All of the above.
I'll get the scissors
and cut that poop off your bum.
Meg, trust me,
you ace these SATs,
you could go on
to do anything.
You could be a doctor,
an architect.
Hell, you could even coach
the Mighty Ducks.
All right, the championship
is on the line.
It's time for a formation
they're not expecting.
The Flying V?
No. The Stinky V.
Wassup, my sistas?
Ooh, I ain't sat down
in a hot minute!
What the hell? Why are
you talking like that?
Sorry, I have
family in town.
You guys, I'm freaking out.
The SATs are this weekend,
and there's no way
I'm gonna get a good score.
You know, Meg, maybe you should
get someone super smart
to take it for you.
Have someone
take it for me?
But that's cheating.
No one cares about
cheating anymore, Meg.
Not since
Slick Willy Clinton
lowered the nation's
moral standards.
God, give it up, Patty.
I'm just saying, find
someone really smart
to take the SAT for you
in exchange for money.
Did someone say
"Jewish"?
Oh, hey, Neil.
Listen, is there
any chance
you'd be willing to take the
SAT for me this weekend?
Sorry, Meg, I'm swamped.
I'm taking my body
into the shop.
I don't know what you've been
doing to this thing, Neil,
but you see this gunk?
That ain't supposed
to be there.
Well, just do
whatever you can.
All right, I'm gonna go eat
a sandwich with one hand
and fill out the invoice
with the other.
Don't worry, Meg.
There's got to
be someone else
who'd be willing to take
that test for you.
Like who?
You guys are my only friends,
and everyone
in my family's a moron.
What about your
hot mom, Meg?
What?
I said how about your dog? He's smart.
That doesn't sound
like what you said,
but yeah,
Brian is kind of smart.
Maybe I'll get him
to take it for me.
Your mom's so  hot.
We now return to another
Michael Jordan
underwear commercial
on a plane for some reason.
Does your underwear
have tags?
Uh, what?
Uh, Mr. Jordan, you're gonna
have to take your seat
and stop asking people
about their underwear.
Oh, hey, Brian.
I was just thinking
about you.
You know how I've always
loved your novel
Faster Than the
Speed of Love?
Okay, what's this?
She's peanut buttering you up
for something.
No, I-I didn't even know
you'd read my novel.
Oh, yeah. I'm a huge
fan of "FATSPOL."
That's the acronym I use for
Faster Than the Speed of Love,
because I mention
it so much.
God, that would've
saved me years.
Anyway, I was just rereading
my favorite passage
the other day.
"The weight of the gun
in Jason's hand surprised him.
'How heavy,' he wondered,
'is the human soul?'"
That's page one.
She's quoting page one.
Your book is genius, Brian.
I can't believe Amazon
is dumping it for 99 cents.
What?! My book is on Amazon?!
Oh, yeah, Brian,
there's something
for everyone on Amazon.
In fact,
you're so smart,
I thought you'd be
the perfect person
to maybe take
the SAT for me.
What? But that would be wrong.
Well, I suppose you may
look at it that way.
But a wise book once said,
"With the heart at stake,
right and wrong is
a stake through the heart."
That one's on the cover.
Wow, ensnared by
my own verbal trap.
Well played, me, through you.
All right, Meg,
I'll take that test for you.
I guess what I'm saying is,
"Ace Pilotson,
reporting for World War Love."
What?
She didn't read  the book, Bri.
That's your
main character.
Don't worry, Meg--
I'm always here to help.
Like a 1960s British policeman.
Officer! Me child's
been kidnapped!
Calm down, ma'am, it's
all under control.
I've got a whistle,
a cloth helmet,
a key to a call box, a
soft rubber truncheon,
and a map of the city.
Please hurry!
I don't much
like your tone.
That's a tiny pencil-and-pad
citation for you!
Okay, Bria you can do this.
Hey, Meg.
Hi, Meg.
Hey, how's it going?
My locker.
Meg, I thought we were
gonna try to work on that.
Hey, other teens,
how about our youth culture,
am I right?
All the new hairs we're getting.
Hey, hashtag SATs, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
Wow, I can't believe
this worked.
I was afraid I'd stick out,
like the one guy
in Lincoln's cabinet
who didn't have a beard.
I want to win this war,
and I want to do it fast. Ideas?
We should meet the rebels
head-on in Virginia.
Yes, and use our ships
to block their supply chains.
We could also use
our troop advantage
to out-flank them
in the west.
Uh, what did that
baby just say?
All right, cell phones away,
eyes on your own paper,
and before we start,
who's giving me a ride home?
Not you, a girl.
For luck, Meg.
We're all rooting for ya.
We now return to Malcolm XXY.
We didn't land on Plymouth Rock!
Yeah!
Plymouth Rock gave us
both sets of genitals!
- Yeah!
- What?
Mail's here.
I got my SAT scores.
So, how'd we do?
"We" scored a thousand.
Nice! One thousand,
on the nose.
Boop! You are welcome.
Brian, that's a thousand
out of a possible 2,400!
That's the worst score
in my class!
What?!
Damn it,
why did I ever think
you were smart?
That's... that's not possible.
Ha-ha! Brian's stupid!
I must alert
the townsfolk!
Hyah! Fly, Artemis, fly!
Hark, townsfolk!
Brian, uh...
he... oh, damn,
what was it?
Brian...
Brian goes to college?
No.
Brian gets
another book published?
Y-Yeah. Yeah,
maybe that's it.
Tell all that Brian's getting
another book published!
Oh, thank God!
I thought it was gonna be
a Meg episode all throughout.
I got the lowest score
in Meg's class?
How could this happen?
Face it, Brian,
this proves that you're stupid.
Proves it empirically.
That means it's verified.
I know!
I just weirdly woke up
in the laundry room.
Not now, Peter!
Geez, what's wrong with you?
Brian took the SAT for Meg,
and it turns out he's an idiot.
That's not true!
Methinks the Hoff
protest a month.
Do you even know what
you're trying to say?
Hey, look, don't feel bad,
Brian-- it's fun being stupid.
You don't got to
worry about nothing,
you don't got to read books,
and you never die.
Peter, that...
that's not correct.
How would you
know, stupid?
Thanks a lot, SAT.
Man, this is
the worst day of my life.
Empirically.
Eh, careful.
Brian, being a dumb
guy's not so awful.
I'll show you. Come on, you're
spending the day with me.
Here, you want a beer?
Peter, it's 11:00 a.m.
If the clock ain't digital,
you don't know that.
Well, actually,
I could use a drink.
There you go! You look
stupider already.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Who cares?
Now, come on,
we're gonna party like
it's the Roaring Twenties.
♪ No TV, movies suck ♪
♪ I'm here with my gal ♪
♪ Shake your hands,
kick around ♪
♪ Wear a suit to breakfast ♪
♪ Underwear that laces up ♪
♪ All girls have
a guy's haircut ♪
♪ Crank your car
to make it start ♪
♪ You will die of measles. ♪
Oh, my God!
Yeah, see, people go
to NASCAR hoping for a crash.
Well, this is all crashes.
But that guy could've been hurt!
Why are you laughing?
'Cause it's funny! What, do you
think you're better than me?
By the way, a huge part
of being an idiot
is constantly
accusing people
of thinking
they're better than you.
That and forwarding
mildly funny e-mails
way after everybody's
already seen them.
Heh. You know this one's funny
'cause there's
seven fonts in 12 colors.
Ha-ha! Dad, I just got
this hilarious e-mail!
You got to see this!
Ha-ha! Chris would love this.
Hey, it looks like
they're shooting T-shirts
into the crowd.
Oh, those aren't T-shirts.
Thems is hot dogs.
Huh. That's
kind of cool.
I want a hot dog.
Well, then you better
move quick-- he's reloading!
Yeah! Free
flying meat!
Hey, you feel good
about yourself, jagoff?
Yeah, that's right-- I knocked
your kid over to get a hot dog.
What, do you think
you're better than me?!
What, you think
You think you're
better than me?!
Ah, look at you, Brian,
right at home with us dumb guys.
You're blending in better than
a centipede among millipedes.
Well, what should
we do today?
Let's try on
1,000 shoes.
Wait a minute.
You're an imposter!
♪ If it hadn't been for
Cotton-Eye Joe ♪
♪ I'd been married
long time ago ♪
♪ Where did you come from,
where did you go? ♪
♪ Where did you
come from, Cotton-Eye Joe? ♪
♪ If it hadn't been
for Cotton-Eye Joe ♪
♪ I'd been married
long time ago ♪
♪ Where did you come from,
where did you go? ♪
♪ Where did you
come from, Cotton-Eye Joe?├О
♪ ♪
♪ If it hadn't been
for Cotton-Eye Joe ♪
♪ I'd been married
long time ago ♪
♪ Where did you come from,
where did you go? ♪
♪ Where did you
come from, Cotton-Eye Joe? ♪
♪ If it hadn't been
for Cotton-Eye Joe ♪
♪ I'd been married
long time ago ♪
♪ Where did you come from,
where did you go? ♪
♪ Where did you
come from, Cotton-Eye Joe? ♪
Hey, yo, Stew.
My boy Peter and I
are watching the Sandler movie
That's My Boy.
You gotta come
check it out, man.
It's amazeballs.
This is just
the DVD menu.
No way.
Aw, man, I am
buzzin' hardcore
off of that chaw, man.
Brian, what
the deuce?
Deuce.
Like poo.
Yes, yes, deuce like poo.
But what the devil
has happened to you?
Uh, I woke up, Kemosabe?
No, I mean it. How
could one bad test score
transform you into
a complete moron?
Brian, I'm concerned something
is very wrong with you.
Nah, man, I've never
felt better, Beef Stew.
Bazinga!
Like what
the gay scientist says.
Hey, Brian,
say something else from TV.
What you talkin' 'bout,
Phyllis?!
Aw, gross,
he's getting his nose period.
Oh, my God! We've got
to get him to a hospital!
Don't worry, Brian,
I'll save you.
I'm good in a crisis.
After all, I used to work
the suicide hotline.
I-I just can't take it.
I discovered my wife's
been cheating on me for a while.
And I just...
I can't live like this.
I have to kill myself.
Doesn't it make more sense
to kill her?
Brian, the good news is
we've stopped the bleeding.
And we've removed
the Matchbox car
that was lodged
in your rectum.
I did that right
after you passed out.
Classic P-Dog.
But, Dr. Hartman,
why did he lose consciousness?
Well, keeping in mind the
recent behavioral changes
you've described,
I did a CAT scan...
On a dog.
We laughed about
that, too.
However, I'm sorry to inform you
that Brian has a brain tumor.
Oh, my God.
There's only one thing to do:
shrink down to microscopic size,
enter Brian's brain,
and destroy the tumor
from within.
I was raped by a bug.
Brain tumor. How
is that possible?
As a father in a hospital
getting bad news,
I am gonna sadly slide down
the wall and take my hat off.
I forgot the hat.
So, Doc, w... um, how much
Jamba Juice do I have to drink
to cure this?
Um...
I-I've also heard that,
like, crystals exist?
Dr. Hartman, do you think
the brain tumor might explain
why Brian's been acting
so odd lately?
Hmm, well, I haven't heard of
brains being linked to behavior,
but I suppose
anything is possible.
Mom, is Dad gonna die?
No, Chris, Brian is the one
with the brain tumor.
Dr. Hartman,
what's the prognosis?
Well, it says here Brian's
tumor is for office use only.
Benign. It says "benign."
Oh, Brian, that's wonderful
news! You're going to be okay!
Winning!
Remember
somebody said that?
Well, since Brian's tumor poses
no immediate threat,
we can schedule surgery
to remove it,
and he'll be back
to his old self in no time.
Well, I say we get that tumor
out of him right away
before he gets any dumber.
No way.
I'm never going back
to my old self.
I rock like this.
I'm legit.
I'm uber.
I'm awesome-sauce.
Either take the tumor out of him
or put one in me!
I can't stand this!
So i-if Brian doesn't have
the surgery,
will he be all right?
I don't know. Is
Dax Shepard all right?
Eh, seems kind
of gratuitous.
My point is, Brian could have
the surgery and be smart again,
or he could skip the surgery
and stay dumb like this.
Well, Brian,
if-if you're happy this way...
Hells to the yeah,
I am!
Hey, um, I was told
there would be a lollipop
at the end of this?
Good, he doesn't know
about the stickers.
I'll take two.
Brian, you're not thinking
clearly, all right?
You've got to agree
to this surgery.
Because right now, you're
as useless as Black Widow is
to the Avengers.
So... what's
your superpower?
Kicking.
Oh, right, 'cause
none of us can kick.
Hey, which one
of you guys can kick?
Hulk, stop being nice.
Sorry.
Hey, this isn't the
Kenny Chesney concert.
No, I'm afraid that was a white
lie to get you here, Brian.
This is the opera.
I'm hoping that re-exposing you
to high culture will remind you
of the joys of a refined mind.
Cool. I'm sitting on my
foot to hold in a dump.
Please don't
embarrass me here.
Pepperoni pie,
extra cheese. G32.
Oh, cool.
My friend Pete is here.
Pete Za.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom. That's
gonna be me in, like, a minute.
Over here, bro!
Aw, I moved my foot.
Hey, this isn't
the Kenny Chesney concert.
No, Brian,
this is called yoga.
Lots of smart people do it
instead of going to church.
And after we get done with this,
you're going to talk a lot
about being present
and grounded.
You're going to be
impossible to be around.
Let's get started.
Whoa! Schwing!
Schwing! Schwing!
That was from
Wayne's World.
That's the sound
of Wayne's boner.
Okay, before
you say anything, no,
this is not
the Kenny Chesney concert.
We're here to have a nice
civilized dinner and to show you
that you don't have to eat
all your meals in your car.
Now, we're going to start
by hearing the waiter
give us the specials.
Good evening. Our first special
is an almond-crusted salmon...
Hey, cram it, skinny.
Give me free food
or I'm gonna tell people on Yelp
there was a pube in my salad.
Free food,
right away.
Okay. All right.
I forgot that Yelp
is a weapon for dumb people.
You taught me something
today, Bri.
That I can throw
a frog a hundred feet?
I can't change you back.
This whole endeavor
was doomed to fail.
Like an Asian guy
going to a salon.
Hi. I want to have
my anus breached.
He's gone, Rupert.
It appears I've lost
Brian to the dumb side.
So now I need you
to be Brian.
Here's your collar.
And here's a laptop.
Write something bad.
"It was the last
day of summer
and the first day of
the rest of her life."
Wow! You did that
with your face!
Hey, what's this?
Gaylord practice?
That's the eighth time
you've asked me that today.
Listen, Brian, I've been trying
to change you.
But I realize
that if you're happy,
I need to accept the you
that you want to be.
No matter how painful that is.
What are you doing?
Oh, my friend Terry told me you
can get high from licking paint.
Who's Terry?
He's friends
with Gus.
Who's Gus?
Um, Gus is
Terry's friend.
It... You kind of
had to be there.
For what?
No story has been told!
Okay, well, I'm gonna go put on
my python and walk to the park.
Brian, wait. I'm...
I'm trying to say that I accept
your choice to forego surgery.
I release you into
the thick mire of stupidity.
Hey, Brian, I started
the car in the garage
and it's all
foggy in there.
Want to go pretend
we're in London?
Oh, totally!
Shrimp on the barbie, huh?
Yes!
Good Lord,
if I don't do something,
his stupidity will kill him.
And then I'd lose Brian forever.
Like that dog
the Russians shot into space.
He made it! Your
dog is in orbit!
Is wonderful.
How do we get him back now?
Oh... about that.
We do not.
Oh, my poor dog.
He will die up there.
Joke on them!
I find happy dog planet.
In 50 years, we all go back
to Earth and bite everybody.
But now we dance!
I've got to convince him
to get that tumor removed
before it's too late.
Now, remember, it's England,
so take long deep breaths.
Wait a second.
I've been approaching this
far too intelligently.
He's an idiot,
so this won't be hard at all.
Hey, Brian, you want
to go see Dr. Hartman
and get that procedure
where you get two wieners?
Whoa! Hell yeah!
That way, when I watch
Black Swan, I can aim one
at Natalie Portman
and aim the other at...
Yes, yes, yes, we all know
who the other one was. Let's go.
Well, good news, Griffins:
Brian is gonna be just fine.
I was able
to remove his tumor.
And if anyone wants to keep it,
it's here in this Tupperware.
This-this is half
of a chicken cutlet.
Oh, boy.
What did I have for lunch?
Oh, Brian, I'm so glad
you're all right.
Thanks. But this is
all kind of surreal.
I mean,
being in this hospital bed,
I-I feel like the main character
of As I Lay Dying
as he or she lay dying.
Oh, that's just the amount of
superficial quasi-knowledge
the old Brian had.
I missed you, buddy.
Welcome back.
Thanks, Stewie.
You never gave up on me.
You knew that wasn't really me.
Yeah, well,
it's no big...
I mean, I was having fun,
making new friends,
getting laid all the time,
sleeping like a rock,
but you made the call.
You unilaterally decided
I was better off
a bitter alcoholic failure who
can only hang out with a baby.
Hey. We have fun.
Hey, Lois, guess what.
I had them do
that two-wiener operation on me.
- You what?!
- Double trouble.
Uh-oh. That was the original.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru